####################################################
#
#  Metadata Plugin Language Translation File
#
#  Copyright 2011 by Andre Wiethoff
#
#####################################################


# Please read these comments before you actually change
# anything in this file (or create a new translation 
# based on it). It contains many hints and explanations
# how such a file has to look like.
# First of all, you have probably noted that everything
# in this file after a '#' character will be ignored
# (and can be used as a comment).
# Of course, you don't need to translate any of the
# comments.

# Next important issue is that all language strings have
# an unique and identifying number to which the string
# is assigned.
# If a number is assigned to a different number, the 
# text of the second number (right side of the equal
# character) is assigned to the number on the left.
# That way, a translation has to be performed only once
# and is copied into a different resource location.
# Usually these lines with two numbers don't need to
# be changed.

# The next question is, what should be translated how.
# Some words are a kind of keywords that MAY NOT
# translated in these files. A second list contains
# words that SHOULD NOT be translated (if anyhow 
# possible)
#
# List of words that MAY NOT be translated :
# (Of course also words that are based on these words)
#
#    Offset
#    Sample
#    CRC
#    Lead-In
#    Lead-Out
#    UPC
#    ISRC
#    CUE Sheet
#    BurnProof
#    ID3 Tag
#    EAC
#    Exact Audio Copy
#    LAME
#    freedb
#    BladeEnc
#    SatCP
#    Session
#    CD-TEXT
#    CDPLAYER.INI
#    ASPI
#
# List of words that SHOULD NOT be translated :
#
#    Track
#    Index
#    CD
#    Burst
#    Pop
#    Glitch
#    FAQ
#    Image   (CD Image)
#    Native  (ASPI Interface)
#    Interpolate
#    Flange
#    Zoom

# The strings that are assigned to the numbers are
# quite easily constructed. All assignments have the
# following look: either
# <number> = <number>
# or
# <number> = <string>
# The first case was already explained; the text from
# the second number will be copied to the first.
# The common case is that a string is assigned that
# needs to be translated.
# A <String> is based on a specific structure, each
# <String> starts and ends with a '"' character; e.g.,
# "This is a test" is a string. If a string is too
# long to fit in a line, it is possible to concat two
# strings into one -- e.g.
# "This is "+
# "a test" 
# will result in the string "This is a test". Please 
# note that the line has to end after the '+' 
# character. And also please note that the <space>
# (empty character) in the first line is necessary,
# as otherwise the string would result in 
# "This isa test".
# In some strings, there are <spaces> at the beginning
# or at the end of the string. Please keep the exact
# number of spaces at that position; e.g. change
# "  This is a test " only to "  Dies ist ein Test ".
# If a string needs to contain the character '"', a
# special code has to be used, as '"' would tell that
# the string is finished. So, whenever the string
# needs the character '"' use the code '\"' instead --
# e.g. "This is a \"test\" file"
# Some strings (for some dialogs) have a '\n' code
# in it. This stands for a carriage return. This is
# only possible within special messages, so when a
# string does not contain such a character, please
# do not add one. It will most probably not work out
# as expected; e.g.
# "This is\n\na test" would look like this:
# This is
#
# a test
# Usually two '\n' codes are used in the strings to
# make such dialogs more easy to read. If there are
# such codes at the end or at the beginning of a 
# string, please also keep these codes untouched.

# The resources are sorted by dialogs and menus as far
# as possible, but at the end of the file, there is a
# list of all other resource strings that were not
# sorted directly into a dialog.
# Please do not change the order of the resource
# numbers, this is important for future updates of
# EAC.

# If there are special needs for information on a
# specific resource, there will be more comments on
# that topic.

# Now, you know all you need to translate this file
# into your language. If you make a mistake, EAC
# will show an error message with the erroneous line
# specified with the exact type of error.
# You should test your translation in small pieces:
# translate e.g. a dialog and then test the translation
# by starting EAC on errors, and that all texts
# are fitting in the reserved space for each resource.
# Also spell-check all your translated texts directly
# in the appropriate dialog. If you don't know exactly
# how to translate a given string, you can have a look
# at the other language definition files that come
# with this EAC.



####################################################
# Plugin General Resources
####################################################

# Please enter here your name that will be shown in
# the EAC About dialog. Translate the rest of the
# line also into your language

    98 = "Tłumaczony przez Gregga"

# Please change the given email address here to your
# email address, so you can be addressed if an error
# in the translation was found.

    99 = "E-Mail: gregg?cdrinfo.pl"

# This is the name of your language in your own
# language

     1 = "Polski"

# This is the name of your language in the english
# language

     2 = "Polish"

# This is the code that is displayed by the program
# showinfo.exe that comes with this SDK. It is the
# locale information from the windows system
# installed on your computer.

     3 = "0415"

# This is the second code number that is shown by
# the showinfo.exe program. It identifies a specific
# language and should be unique for each language.

     4 = "C364D3AE"

# The following strings are very common strings that
# are used very often in the dialogs etc.

     5 = "Błąd"
     6 = "Ostrzeżenie"
     7 = "Sukces"
     8 = "Informacja"
     9 = "Pytanie"

    10 = "OK"
    11 = "Anuluj"
    12 = "Zastosuj"
    15 = "Tak"
    16 = "Nie"
    
    40 = "1.4"


####################################################
# Metadata plugin - Options Dialog
####################################################

   100 = "Opcje"
   
   101 = "Wtyczka metadanych MusicBrainz"
   102 = "Napisana w 2020 roku przez Andre Wiethoffa"
   103 = "Wtyczka należy do Domeny Publicznej i można ją dowolnie kopiować, używać i modyfikować!"
   
   104 = "Użyj następującegio serwera MusicBrainz"
   
   105 = "Poszukaj okładki po owocnym zakończeniu przeszukiwania fredb"
   106 = "Poszukaj słów piosenek po owocnym zakończeniu przeszukiwania fredb"
   
   107 = "Nigdy"
   108 = "Zapytaj"
   109 = "Zawsze"
   
   110 = "Błąd podczas przeszukiwania listy serwerów!"
   111 = "Nieprawidłowy adres serwera MusicBrainz server!\n\nOdrzucić zmiany?"
   
   120 = "Wtyczka metadanych MusicBrainz"
   
####################################################
# Plugin Multiple CD Selection
####################################################

   200 = "Wybór płyty"
   
   201 = "Znaleziono kilka pasujących pozycji. Wybierz właściwą lub najlepiej pasującą!"
   
   
   
####################################################
# Metadata plugin - CD Cover Downloader
####################################################

   300 = "Pobieranie okładek"
   
   301 = "Kryteria wyszukiwania:"
   
   302 = "Sortowanie:"
   303 = "Przenieś wybrane okładki do EAC-a"
   304 = "Proszę wybrać jeden lub więcej rodzajów obrazków "+
         "wymienionych poniżej aby rozpocząć wyszukiwanie."
         
   305 = "Małe obrazki"
   306 = "Średnie obrazki"
   307 = "Duże obrazki"
   
   308 = "Wyszukiwanie"
   309 = "Zrobione"
   310 = "Stop"
   
   311 = "Nieposortowane"
   312 = "Najpierw większe obrazki"
   313 = "Najpierw większe pliki"
   314 = "Najlepszy współczynnik"
   316 = "Group Similar Pictures"
   
   315 = "Zapisz plik obrazka"
         
 
####################################################
# Metadata plugin - Status Dialog
####################################################

   400 = "Pobieranie danych z MusicBrainz"
   
   401 = "Stan pobierania informacji o płycie:"
   402 = "Wysyłanie żądania"
   
   403 = "Nie można połączyć się z MusicBrainz!"
   404 = "Nie znaleziono żadnych informacji o tej płycie!"
   405 = "Wpis w bazie danych jest uszkodzony!"
   406 = "Brak potwierdzenia!"
   407 = "Nieznany błąd!"
   408 = "Pobieranie metadanych"
   409 = "Błąd podczas łączenia z MusicBrainz!"
   
   410 = "Czy chcesz teraz poszukać okładek?"
   411 = "Czy chcesz teraz poszukać słów piosenek?"



####################################################
# Metadata plugin - Lyrics Selection
####################################################

   500 = "Wybór słów piosenek"
   
   501 = "Zaakceptuj"
   502 = "Mniejsza z tym"

   503 = "Proszę wybrać słowa piosenki"
   504 = "Twórca"
   505 = "Tytuł"
   506 = "Słowa"
   507 = "Ponów szukanie"
   

  
####################################################
# Metadata plugin - FreeDB Submission
####################################################
   
   600 = "Zły rodzaj muzyki MusicBrainz!\nMie można wysłać tych danych dopóki "+
         "nie zostanie skorygowany rodzaj muzyki na zgodny z wymogami MusicBrainz!"


