####################################################
#
#  Metadata Plugin Language Translation File
#
#  Copyright 2011 by Andre Wiethoff
#
#####################################################


# Please read these comments before you actually change
# anything in this file (or create a new translation 
# based on it). It contains many hints and explanations
# how such a file has to look like.
# First of all, you have probably noted that everything
# in this file after a '#' character will be ignored
# (and can be used as a comment).
# Of course, you don't need to translate any of the
# comments.

# Next important issue is that all language strings have
# an unique and identifying number to which the string
# is assigned.
# If a number is assigned to a different number, the 
# text of the second number (right side of the equal
# character) is assigned to the number on the left.
# That way, a translation has to be performed only once
# and is copied into a different resource location.
# Usually these lines with two numbers don't need to
# be changed.

# The next question is, what should be translated how.
# Some words are a kind of keywords that MAY NOT
# translated in these files. A second list contains
# words that SHOULD NOT be translated (if anyhow 
# possible)
#
# List of words that MAY NOT be translated :
# (Of course also words that are based on these words)
#
#    Offset
#    Sample
#    CRC
#    Lead-In
#    Lead-Out
#    UPC
#    ISRC
#    CUE Sheet
#    BurnProof
#    ID3 Tag
#    EAC
#    Exact Audio Copy
#    LAME
#    freedb
#    BladeEnc
#    SatCP
#    Session
#    CD-TEXT
#    CDPLAYER.INI
#    ASPI
#
# List of words that SHOULD NOT be translated :
#
#    Track
#    Index
#    CD
#    Burst
#    Pop
#    Glitch
#    FAQ
#    Image   (CD Image)
#    Native  (ASPI Interface)
#    Interpolate
#    Flange
#    Zoom

# The strings that are assigned to the numbers are
# quite easily constructed. All assignments have the
# following look: either
# <number> = <number>
# or
# <number> = <string>
# The first case was already explained; the text from
# the second number will be copied to the first.
# The common case is that a string is assigned that
# needs to be translated.
# A <String> is based on a specific structure, each
# <String> starts and ends with a '"' character; e.g.,
# "This is a test" is a string. If a string is too
# long to fit in a line, it is possible to concat two
# strings into one -- e.g.
# "This is "+
# "a test" 
# will result in the string "This is a test". Please 
# note that the line has to end after the '+' 
# character. And also please note that the <space>
# (empty character) in the first line is necessary,
# as otherwise the string would result in 
# "This isa test".
# In some strings, there are <spaces> at the beginning
# or at the end of the string. Please keep the exact
# number of spaces at that position; e.g. change
# "  This is a test " only to "  Dies ist ein Test ".
# If a string needs to contain the character '"', a
# special code has to be used, as '"' would tell that
# the string is finished. So, whenever the string
# needs the character '"' use the code '\"' instead --
# e.g. "This is a \"test\" file"
# Some strings (for some dialogs) have a '\n' code
# in it. This stands for a carriage return. This is
# only possible within special messages, so when a
# string does not contain such a character, please
# do not add one. It will most probably not work out
# as expected; e.g.
# "This is\n\na test" would look like this:
# This is
#
# a test
# Usually two '\n' codes are used in the strings to
# make such dialogs more easy to read. If there are
# such codes at the end or at the beginning of a 
# string, please also keep these codes untouched.

# The resources are sorted by dialogs and menus as far
# as possible, but at the end of the file, there is a
# list of all other resource strings that were not
# sorted directly into a dialog.
# Please do not change the order of the resource
# numbers, this is important for future updates of
# EAC.

# If there are special needs for information on a
# specific resource, there will be more comments on
# that topic.

# Now, you know all you need to translate this file
# into your language. If you make a mistake, EAC
# will show an error message with the erroneous line
# specified with the exact type of error.
# You should test your translation in small pieces:
# translate e.g. a dialog and then test the translation
# by starting EAC on errors, and that all texts
# are fitting in the reserved space for each resource.
# Also spell-check all your translated texts directly
# in the appropriate dialog. If you don't know exactly
# how to translate a given string, you can have a look
# at the other language definition files that come
# with this EAC.



####################################################
# Plugin General Resources
####################################################

# Please enter here your name that will be shown in
# the EAC About dialog. Translate the rest of the
# line also into your language

    98 = "Översatt av Per Målare"

# Please change the given email address here to your
# email address, so you can be addressed if an error
# in the translation was found.

    99 = "E-Mail : malare?nordsp.se"

# This is the name of your language in your own
# language

     1 = "Svenska"

# This is the name of your language in the english
# language

     2 = "Swedish"

# This is the code that is displayed by the program
# showinfo.exe that comes with this SDK. It is the
# locale information from the windows system
# installed on your computer.

     3 = "041d"

# This is the second code number that is shown by
# the showinfo.exe program. It identifies a specific
# language and should be unique for each language.

     4 = "F94A8C3C"

# The following strings are very common strings that
# are used very often in the dialogs etc.

     5 = "Felmeddelande"
     6 = "Varning"
     7 = "Framgångsrik"
     8 = "Information"
     9 = "Fråga"

    10 = "OK"
    11 = "Avbryt"
    12 = "Verkställ"
    15 = "Ja"
    16 = "Nej"
    
    40 = "1.4"


####################################################
# Metadata plugin - Options Dialog
####################################################

   100 = "Inställningar"
   
   101 = "MusicBrainz metadataplugin"
   102 = "Skriven 2020 av Andre Wiethoff"
   103 = "Denna plugin är Public Domain, du kan använda, modifiera "+
         "och kopiera den såsom du önskar!"
   
   104 = "Använd MusicBrainz server"
   
   105 = "Öppna omslagssökning efter framgångsrik MusicBrainz hämtning"
   106 = "Sök efter texter efter framgångsrik MusicBrainz hämtning"
   
   107 = "Aldrig"
   108 = "Be om det"
   109 = "Alltid"
   
   110 = "Fel vid hämtning av serverlista!"
   111 = "Felaktig MusicBrainz server URL!\n\nFörkasta ändringarna?"
   
   120 = "MusicBrainz Metadata Plugin"
   
####################################################
# Plugin Multiple CD Selection
####################################################

   200 = "CD Val"
   
   201 = "Hittade en mångfald CD, välj den korrekta från listan!"
   
   
   
####################################################
# Metadata plugin - CD Cover Downloader
####################################################

   300 = "CD Omslagsbild Nerladdning"
   
   301 = "Sökvillkor:"
   
   302 = "Sorterar resultat:"
   303 = "Överför valt omslag till EAC"
   304 = "Välj en eller flera bildförsörjare från urvalet nedan för "+
         "att starta sökningen."
         
   305 = "Små Bilder"
   306 = "Medium Bilder"
   307 = "Stora Bilder"
   
   308 = "Söker"
   309 = "Färdig"
   310 = "Stopp"
   
   311 = "Ingen Sortering"
   312 = "Stora Bilder Först"
   313 = "Stora Filer Först"
   314 = "Bästa Förhållande"
   316 = "Group Similar Pictures"
   
   315 = "Spara Bildfil"
         
 
####################################################
# Metadata plugin - Status Dialog
####################################################

   400 = "MusicBrainz Databas Förfrågan"
   
   401 = "Status nerladdning CD-information"
   402 = "Startar begärd nerladdning"
   
   403 = "Kan inte ansluta till MusicBrainz!"
   404 = "Ingen CD-information hittades!"
   405 = "Databasposten är felaktig!"
   406 = "Ingen handskakning!"
   407 = "Okänt fel!"
   408 = "Laddar ner metadata"
   409 = "Fel vid anslutning till MusicBrainz!"
   
   410 = "Vill du söka efter omslagsbilder nu?"
   411 = "Vill du söka efter sångtexter nu?"



####################################################
# Metadata plugin - Lyrics Selection
####################################################

   500 = "Sångtextval"
   
   501 = "Godkänn"
   502 = "Bry dig inte om det"

   503 = "Välj en sångtext för detta spår"
   504 = "Artist"
   505 = "Titel"
   506 = "Sångtexter"
   507 = "Ny Sökning"
   

  
####################################################
# Metadata plugin - FreeDB Submission
####################################################
   
   600 = "Felaktig MusicBrainz musikstil!\nKan inte överföra data förrän "+
         "MusicBrainz musikstilen är korrigerad!"


